{"data":[{"question":"She was no longer alive. She _____ years ago.","a":"has died","b":"had died","c":"has die","d":"had die","answer":"2","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\nAction \"died\"  lead to \" no longer live\"\n+ Structudre: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She _____ to me like that before.","a":"never speaks","b":"had never spoken","c":"never spoke","d":"is never spoken","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Express the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't recognise him. He _______ a lot.","a":"changcd","b":"has changed","c":"had changed","d":"is changed","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n-Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"changed\" lead to \" I didn't recognised him\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She saw that the cinema _____ down.","a":"had closed","b":"has clossed","c":"closed","d":"is closed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"closed\" happened before action \"saw\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I noticed that he _____ anything all evening.","a":"didn't say","b":"hasn't said","c":"hadn't said","d":"hadn't told","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Express the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...) ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She was afraid because she _______ before.","a":"had never flown","b":"didn't fly","c":"has never flown","d":"don't fly","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \" never flown\" lead to \"afraid\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"My friends were no longer there. They _____.","a":"have leave","b":"have left","c":"had leave","d":"had left","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past: \n + Action \"left\" lead to \" no longer there\" \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...) ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"They didn't come. They _____ something else.","a":"have arranged","b":"have arrange","c":"had arranged","d":"are arranged","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"arranged something else\" lead to \" they didn't come\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Her eyes were red. She _____.","a":"has been crying","b":"had been crying","c":"was crying","d":"is been crying","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous:\n- Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past; however, the duration does not continue until now, it stops before something else in the past.\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...) been +V_ing+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The house was dirty. She _______ it for ages,","a":"hadn't cleaned","b":"hasn't cleaned","c":"hadn't clean","d":"hasn't clean","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \" not cleaned\" lead to \" dirty\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}